question_data = [
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The word &quot;news&quot; originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The average woman is 5 inches / 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
]